[{"answer": "Well we, Piers as you know, we just covered this last night, what exactly is free speech to me really have free speech in this country.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "You as a high profile gay black man, I mean what is your reaction to this?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I hug all my teachers just to show appreciation on what they do from me.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Why did you hug your teacher?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes plenty of time 4 to 5 times.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "And have you hugged this teacher before?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Well, just a few (ph) even if they haven't teach and taught me.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Four to 5 times and other teachers?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "This particular teacher apparently says that she warned you not to hug her is that true?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Yeah, other students hug teachers -- other teachers.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Did other students hug the teachers?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "No, sir.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "You don't think there's anything inappropriate about what you did?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "I mean, I describe my self as a well-mannered man and I'm basically about to be 18 so I'm well on my way.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Are you mischievous how do you describe yourself?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "No sir.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "She apparently said in the discipline report that your lips touched the back of her neck and chick did they?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "I was just thinking about senior year and what am I going to do for my education, like my heart dropped like I didn't know what to do.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "I mean what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "In a sense, I feel more cautious and what -- how I go about greeting people and if they -- if I do go at least hesitate for -- just like oh, wait no.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Has it stopped you hugging people?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Well the appeal has been sent in today, so we have to wait for the board to make a decision on are they going to reinstate him along back in school.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "And (inaudible) is there any leave of appeal here, do you got any last recourse to try and get this changed?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Yes sir", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "I hope the school see sense because your pretty good sportsman, right?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Definitely.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "So they think you're back in the team?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "She paid this housekeeper exactly what she promised to pay her well above the minimum wage.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "But just to clarify are you saying that your client did pay this housekeeper the minimum wage or above?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Well, that's exactly what happened.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "It did seem absolutely crazy, is that true, did that happen?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "I've spent an enormous amount of time with my client and just to set the record straight.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "I mean, have you talked to your client directly about that particular part of it?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Because the journalist was asking me to keep quiet about something that I've been so passionate about and the problem in India of this gang rape.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "What was it the journalist asked you?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Has it reinforce your view that things must change in India?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "I think father's blessings are very important.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "How do you feel about the fact that you have no relationship with your father?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Really, of course were social with each other, like on occasions, like Christmas and family weddings we meet each other.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Have you heard from him at all since you had such success with films?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "HEREWAT: Very sad, yes.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Sad isn't it?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Not anymore.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Do you worry about that?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "You know, there's been a resistance for so long, ever since my father married her.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Why does your stepmother Jean (ph) have such a resistance to seeing your father?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "We're not allowed to say that either else visitations can get pulled.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "A part of it is sort of absurd legal barriers we face here but how was your father when you saw him?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "And you have grandchildren as well, any children between you?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Wow, I mean ...", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Your stepmother Jean (ph), talk to her and you tell her, what would you say to her?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Piers, we said everything we needed to say to her whether it's in to a camera, whether it's to you, whether it's to a judge or to our lawyers.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "What do you want to say to this person to try and make her see and let, two obviously loving children see their father?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "My father's biggest joy in life was his family and his friends.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Is she the -- let's try and play devil's advocate is part of the reason she's doing this that she doesn't want people to see your father in the condition that he's in?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Did you ever know that you're my hero.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "You know if you could choose any song of all the songs to dedicate to your father right now, which one would you go for?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "How would she have said that too and this isn't going to be easy to me.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "What was it you wanted to tell me, darling?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Well, it wasn't ...", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "How could you?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Well it -- I haven't read the book, but I understand that it's very good.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "How are you Tim, I mean you, when you finish this book what did you conclude about your extraordinary life?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "It was marvelous.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "What was it like when you first began to work they realized you have this extraordinary chemistry?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well she's very giving and very -- she's just wonderful, you know, its -- you can not anger her by any means.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "What made Carol so special?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Well I have a natural humor about me and when I talk to people that comes out, you know.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Are you naturally like that or is it always quite hard work for you to perform?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "They've been bouncing of walls about this.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "And even you wouldn't know what was going?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "We never cracked up on purpose ever, ever, ever.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "So what -- so is that why kept cracking up so much is that you just couldn't -- you didn't know what's happening next?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Well, there's -- that's just -- dyslexia helped me out a lot because I would get up to read in class and I couldn't.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "How did you get to be funny?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "URNETT: Did you tell Piers about the doorbell?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Do you find it offensive the modern kind of way of telling pretty crude jokes?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Do you dislike it?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "ONWAY: I would go holdup a bank.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "If you -- If I say it right, you've got five minutes to live, you can tell one joke again before you peg it, what would it be?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "I do a sit down now.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Do you still do stand up on the occasion?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Would you ever bank your joke a little err, if it's not going great?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "You don't tell jokes.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "If you got one you pull out the ether?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Do you find everything pretty funny?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "Newhart is pretty funny.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "... who's a professional comedian?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Well ...", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Carol, what would you say?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Well, I like -- they're apples and oranges.", "docId": "131218pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "You could pay to see one comedian on stage again, who would you choose?", "qSentId": 606}]